[Waco] Daughters of the American Revolution: Henry Downs Chapter records, Inclusive: 1897-2006, undated, Bulk: 1960-1990
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Literary Productions, 1900-2001; 5
  - Program: Eighty-Fourth Continental Congress: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Program: Ninetieth Continental Congress: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Program: Ninety-Second Continental Congress: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Program: Ninety-Third Continental Congress: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Program: Thirty-First Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1930 November 3-6 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Program: Fifty-Second and Fifty-Third Annual Conferences: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1951, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Program: Fifty-Fifth and Fifty-Eighth Annual Conferences: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1954, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Program: Sixtieth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Program: Sixty-First Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1960 March 8-11 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Program: Sixty-Second Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1961 February 16-18 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Program: Sixty-Sixth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1965 March 16-18 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Program: Sixty-Seventh Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1966 March 15-17 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Program: Sixty-Ninth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1968 March 12-14 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Program: Seventieth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1969 March 17-19 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Program: Seventy-First Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1970 March 26-28 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Program: Seventy-Third Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Program: Seventy-Fourth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Program: Diamond Anniversary Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Program: Seventy-Sixth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1975 March 18-20 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Program: Seventy-Seventh Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1976 March 16-18 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Program: Seventy-Eighth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1977 March 22-24 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Program: Seventy-Ninth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1978 March 7-9 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Program: Eighty-First Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Program: Eighty-Third Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Program: Eighty-Fifth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Yearbooks: William Alexander Society, 1933-1934, 1934-1935 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Yearbooks: William Alexander Society, 1937-1937 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1902-1903, 1905-1906 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1913-1914 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1922-1923, 1927-1928 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1930-1931, 1931-1932 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1936-1937, 1937-1938 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1938-1939, 1939-1940 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1940-1941, 1941-1942 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1942-1943, 1943-1944 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1945-1946, 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1947-1948, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1949-1950, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1951-1952, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1953-1954, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1955-1956, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1959-1960, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1961-1962, 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1964-1966, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1968-1969, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1970-1971, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1972-1973, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1974-1975, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1976-1977, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1978-1979, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1982-1983, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Yearbooks: Henry Downs Chapter, 1984-1985, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Essay: “Genealogical Research for National Society Daughters of the American Revolution”, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Essay: Lipa De La Rosa: Concerning Abigail Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Essay: Stephanie Mansfield: Concerning Abigail Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Essay: Wanda Adams: Concerning John Adams, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Essay: Joey Culpepper: Concerning John Adams, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Essay: Jenifer Elkins: Concerning John Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Essay: Lamont Hall: Concerning John Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Essay: Monica Hernandez: Concerning John Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Essay: Tereasa Hunt: Concerning John Adams, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Essay: Ricki Marshall: Concerning John Adams, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Essay: Tracy Miller: Concerning John Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Essay: Laura Patricia: Concerning John Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Essay: Blake Petty: Concerning John Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Essay: Christopher Porter: Concerning John Adams, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Essay: John Rhodes, Jr.: Concerning John Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Essay: LuChana Sauseda: Concerning John Adams, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Essay: Scott Wittschen: Concerning John Adams, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Essay: Gabrielle Bush: Concerning Samuel Adams, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Essay: Carl Gulley: Concerning Samuel Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Essay: Anna Martin: Concerning Samuel Adams, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Essay: Brian Vinarick: Concerning Samuel Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Essay: Eugene Webb: Concerning Samuel Adams, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Essay: Elizabeth Buchanon: Concerning African Americans in Revolution, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Essay: Shannon Johnson: Concerning African Americans in Revolution, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Essay: Jeff Lee: Concerning African Americans in Revolution, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Essay: Richard Mills: Concerning African Americans in Revolution, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Essay: Lloyd Rose: Concerning African Americans in Revolution, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Essay: Robert Bills: Concerning Ethan Allen, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Essay: Jennifer Kraemer: Concerning Ethan Allen, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Essay: James McLellan: Concerning Ethan Allen, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Essay: Courtney Shows: Concerning Ethan Allen, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Essay: Amy Tieman: Concerning Ethan Allen, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Essay: Brandi Howe: Concerning John Andre, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Essay: Patricia Fellers: Concerning Apaches, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Essay: Roger Recindus: Concerning John Appleby, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Essay: Melissa Kolinck: Benedict Arnold, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Essay: Curry Kenworthy: Benedict Arnold, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Essay: Pete Maja: Benedict Arnold, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Essay: Marva Griffin: Concerning Crispus Attucks, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Essay: Christian Howald: Concerning Crispus Attucks, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Essay: DeAnna Martin: Concerning Stephen Austin, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Essay: Lacy Henderson: Concerning Alexander Graham Bell, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Essay: Meredith O’Dowd: Concerning Alexander Graham Bell, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Essay: Curtis Wood: Concerning Alexander Graham Bell, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Essay: Amy Jasek: Concerning David Bushnell, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Essay: Jonathan Ketcham: Concerning George Rogers Clark, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Essay: John Powell: Concerning George Rogers Clark, undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Essay: Rachel Simonette: Concerning George Rogers Clark, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Essay: Alexandra Nevarez: Concerning Henry Clay, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Essay: Bobby Abrahams: Concerning Samuel Colt, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Essay: Jeremy Echols: Concerning Samuel Colt, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Essay: Gary Humphrey: Concerning Samuel Colt, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Essay: Shelley Barker: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Essay: Tiffany Dale: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Essay: Sherrie Davis: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Essay: Michael Gulen: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Essay: Alison Hayward: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Essay: Illya Hicks: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Essay: Melissa Huitt: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Essay: Reshma Jagsi: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Essay: Kevin Lintz: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Essay: Kandi Martin: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Essay: Kristi Norton: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Essay: Heather Robertson: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Essay: Brandon Ross: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Essay: Christine Shaw: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Essay: Blanca Sierra: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Essay: Michele Steele: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Essay: Jennifer Swanson: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Essay: Cara Walding: Concerning Constitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Essay: Perry Weaver: Concerning Constitution, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Essay: James E. Hughes: Concerning Peter Cooper, undated (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Essay: Stephanie Arocha: Concerning Margaret Corbin, undated (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Essay: Mike Chaney: Concerning Davy Crockett, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Essay: Kristi Henry: Concerning John Deere, undated (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Essay: Joseph Lynch: Concerning John Deere, undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Essay: Kendra Adkism: Concerning John Dickinson, undated (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Essay: Angel Allen: Concerning Frederick Douglass, undated (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Essay: Justin Ducharme: Concerning Thomas Edison, undated (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Essay: Collin Hoag: Concerning Thomas Edison, undated (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Essay: Karen King: Concerning Thomas Edison, undated (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Essay: Erin McNamara: Concerning Thomas Edison, undated (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Essay: Lygina Weaver: Concerning Thomas Edison, undated (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Essay: Kerry Wiley: Concerning Oliver Evans, undated (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Essay: Rastin Reisinger: Concerning Federalist #86, undated (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Essay: Melissa Nelson: Concerning Food, undated (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Essay: Angie Akins: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Essay: Elizabeth Atkins: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Essay: Jayson Bales: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Essay: John Bardin, Jr.: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Essay: Blayn Barnard: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Essay: Norma Barragail: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Essay: Lance Brewer: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Essay: Rosalinda Bravo: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Essay: Dung Chile: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Essay: Susanne Christian: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Essay: Jennifer Curry: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Essay: Alison Ellis: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Essay: Kathy Gaitros: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Essay: Kim Griffith: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Essay: Michel Johnson: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Essay: Heidi Koch: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Essay: Melissa Kolinek: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Essay: Carrie Kramalis: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Essay: Susan Layne: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Essay: Steve Leilgahn: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Essay: Kimberly McKenzie: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Essay: Ellen Montemayer: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Essay: Meredith O’Dowd: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Essay: Neal Palomino: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Essay: Jennifer Raiffeisen: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Essay: Jody Riggs: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Essay: Luke Roberts: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Essay: Rachel Roberts: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Essay: Scott Segrest: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Essay: Scotty Shoultz: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Essay: Alisha Springer: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Essay: Mike Turk: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Essay: Demarcus Young: Concerning Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Essay: John Cubbison: Concerning Robert Fulton, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Essay: Joel Edwards: Concerning Robert Fulton, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Essay: LaKisha Foley: Concerning Robert Fulton, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Essay: Sonya Hennig: Concerning Robert Fulton, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Essay: Blake Masters: Concerning Robert Fulton, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Essay: Joni Minai: Concerning Robert Fulton, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Essay: Jimmy Stones: Concerning Robert Fulton, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Essay: Brad Hodge: Concerning Horatio Gates, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Essay: Gabriel Jones: Concerning Horatio Gates:, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Essay: Rudy Soza: Concerning Carlos Glidden and Christopher Sholes, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Essay: Shellie McNary: Concerning Glassmaking, undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Essay: Leigh Gofoith: Concerning Charles Goodyear, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Essay: Todd Myers: Concerning Charles Goodyear, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Essay: Shellie Streetman: Concerning Elisha Grey, undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Essay: Felipa Hitchcock: Concerning Nathan Hale, undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Essay: Leena Patel: Concerning Nathan Hale, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Essay: Amber Pooley: Concerning Nathan Hale, undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Essay: John Whittenburg: Concerning Nathan Hale, undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Essay: Harold Bryant: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Essay: Christi Cox: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Essay: Jay Feight: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Essay: Deana Hanks: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Essay: Emily Hunter-Kultgen: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Essay: Jason Lane: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Essay: Scott Masters: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Essay: Zack Myers: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Essay: James Pyle III: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Essay: Scott Smith: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Essay: Melissa Waden: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Essay: Edward Wucker: Concerning Alexander Hamilton, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Essay: Aaron Battles: Concerning John Hancock, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Essay: Della Grusendorf: Concerning John Hancock, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Essay: Lacy Litton: Concerning John Hancock, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Essay: Elaine Morgan: Concerning John Hancock, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Essay: Emma Villa: Concerning John Hancock, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Essay: Calvin Bailey: Concerning Mary Ludwig Hays, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Essay: Christopher Allen: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Essay: Patrick Canuth: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Essay: John Cubbison: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Essay: Denise Dawson: Concerning Patrick Henry, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Essay: Amanda Duckworth: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Essay: Lynna Garland: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Essay: Kim Jager: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Essay: Rachel Miller: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Essay: Emily Murphy: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Essay: Tim Stacy: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Essay: Becky Stephens: Concerning Patrick Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Essay: Lisle Taylor: Concerning Thomas Heyward, Jr., undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Essay: Rachel Munoz: Concerning Richard Hoe, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Essay: Tim Stacy: Concerning John Holland, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Essay: Candice Woodham: Concerning Sam Houston, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Essay: Justina Johnson: Concerning Elias Howe, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Essay: Kyle Nash: Concerning Elias Howe, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Essay: Shannon Sowder: Concerning John Jay, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Essay: Connor Bales: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Essay: Ned Barrier: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Essay: Mary C. Battles: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Essay: Amy Beck: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Essay: Shari Brandon: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Essay: Travis Brewer: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Essay: Heather Brink: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Essay: Martin Coleman: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Essay: Jennifer Cross: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Essay: Carla Ervin: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Essay: Shelley Freeman: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Essay: Nancy Guerrero: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Essay: Steven Hoag: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Essay: Emily Hunter-Kultgen: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Essay: Ryan Lindsey: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Essay: Jerry O’Quinn: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Essay: Christen Weaver: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Essay: Erin Wilson: Concerning Thomas Jefferson, undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Essay: Brandon Bentle: Concerning John Paul Jones, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Essay: Jeremy Echols: Concerning John Paul Jones, undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Essay: Collin Cox: Concerning John Paul Jones, undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Essay: Clay Johnston: Concerning John Paul Jones, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Essay: Lindsay Little: Concerning John Paul Jones, undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Essay: Joseph Lynch: Concerning John Paul Jones, undated (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Essay: Houston Oates: Concerning John Paul Jones, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Essay: Demetrius Williams: Concerning John Paul Jones, undated (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Essay: Eugene Yedinah: Concerning John Paul Jones, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Essay: Michael Lumpkin: Concerning Henry Knox, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Essay: Joanna Dewald: Concerning LaFayette, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Essay: Ruben Palkin: Concerning LaFayette, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Essay: Lori Teichelmann: Concerning LaFayette, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Essay: Anne Harper: Concerning Jean Laffite, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Essay: Daniel Urban: Concerning Samuel Langley, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Essay: Amy Jasek: Concerning Henry Laurens, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Essay: Joel Edwards: Concerning Richard Henry Lee, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Essay: Erin Wilson: Concerning Richard Henry Lee, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Essay: Kelly Woodliff: Concerning Richard Henry Lee, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Essay: LeeAnn Conaway: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Essay: Richard Conner: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Essay: Tiffany Dale: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Essay: Damon Edwards: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Essay: Andrew Hall: Concerning James Madison, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Essay: Jonah Herbert: Concerning James Madison, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Essay: Karen King: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Essay: Jason Lane: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Essay: Jim McNiel: Concerning James Madison, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Essay: Melody Sanders: Concerning James Madison, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)